[    
	{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "be",
        "respuesta": "was/were / been",
        "incorrecta1": "i / was",
        "incorrecta2": "wes / wis",
        "incorrecta3": "wais / wais"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "beat",
        "respuesta": "beat / beaten",
        "incorrecta1": "beated / beaten",
        "incorrecta2": "biit / biiten",
        "incorrecta3": "beat / beit"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "become",
        "respuesta": "became / become",
        "incorrecta1": "becaime / become",
        "incorrecta2": "bicam / became",
        "incorrecta3": "beccome / becaime"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "begin",
        "respuesta": "began / begun",
        "incorrecta1": "begane / begun",
        "incorrecta2": "bigann / beigan",
        "incorrecta3": "begun / begin"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "bite",
        "respuesta": "bit / bitten",
        "incorrecta1": "bited / bited",
        "incorrecta2": "bit / bited",
        "incorrecta3": "beit / beit"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "break",
        "respuesta": "broke / broken",
        "incorrecta1": "broken / breik",
        "incorrecta2": "bruk / broken",
        "incorrecta3": "break / breik"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "bring",
        "respuesta": "brought / brought",
        "incorrecta1": "brught / brang",
        "incorrecta2": "broutgh / breight",
        "incorrecta3": "breight / bring"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "build",
        "respuesta": "built / built",
        "incorrecta1": "builden / build",
        "incorrecta2": "buil / build",
        "incorrecta3": "bould / bold"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "buy",
        "respuesta": "bought / bought",
        "incorrecta1": "bught / broutgh",
        "incorrecta2": "bougth / bougth",
        "incorrecta3": "bught / bught"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "can",
        "respuesta": "could / -",
        "incorrecta1": "cud / -",
        "incorrecta2": "coult / -",
        "incorrecta3": "couldt / -"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "catch",
        "respuesta": "caught / caught",
        "incorrecta1": "cught / caught",
        "incorrecta2": "cought / cought",
        "incorrecta3": "catch / catch"
    },
    {
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "choose",
        "respuesta": "chose / chosen",
        "incorrecta1": "chossen / chossen",
        "incorrecta2": "chouse / chosen",
        "incorrecta3": "chuze / chosen"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "come",
        "respuesta": "came / come",
        "incorrecta1": "caame / came",
        "incorrecta2": "cume / cumen",
        "incorrecta3": "kame / kome"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "cost",
        "respuesta": "cost / cost",
        "incorrecta1": "coust / cost",
        "incorrecta2": "costen / cost",
        "incorrecta3": "caoust / coust"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "cut",
        "respuesta": "cut / cut",
        "incorrecta1": "cout / cout",
        "incorrecta2": "kut / kut",
        "incorrecta3": "cat / cat"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "do",
        "respuesta": "did / done",
        "incorrecta1": "dyd / dyd",
        "incorrecta2": "dide / done",
        "incorrecta3": "deid / do"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "draw",
        "respuesta": "drew / drawn",
        "incorrecta1": "driw / driw",
        "incorrecta2": "drouw / drawn",
        "incorrecta3": "drit / drew"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "dream",
        "respuesta": "dreamt / dreamt",
        "incorrecta1": "dreimt / dreimt",
        "incorrecta2": "draimt / dreamt",
        "incorrecta3": "droum / droum"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "drink",
        "respuesta": "drank / drunk",
        "incorrecta1": "dranke / dranke",
        "incorrecta2": "drounk / drounk",
        "incorrecta3": "drounk / drank"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "drive",
        "respuesta": "drove / driven",
        "incorrecta1": "drouve / drouve",
        "incorrecta2": "drouvt / drouven",
        "incorrecta3": "droved / driven"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "eat",
        "respuesta": "ate / eaten",
        "incorrecta1": "eit / eit",
        "incorrecta2": "it / iten",
        "incorrecta3": "eited / eited"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "fall",
        "respuesta": "fell / fallen",
        "incorrecta1": "fill / fall",
        "incorrecta2": "foull / foull",
        "incorrecta3": "fall / fallen"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "feel",
        "respuesta": "felt / felt",
        "incorrecta1": "filt / filt",
        "incorrecta2": "feilt / feilt",
        "incorrecta3": "feelt / feelt"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "find",
        "respuesta": "found / found",
        "incorrecta1": "fund / fund",
        "incorrecta2": "fouin / found",
        "incorrecta3": "fownd / fownd"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "fly",
        "respuesta": "flew / flown",
        "incorrecta1": "fliw / fliw",
        "incorrecta2": "flawou / flawou",
        "incorrecta3": "fleid / fleid"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "forget",
        "respuesta": "forgot / forgotten",
        "incorrecta1": "fourgot / fourgot",
        "incorrecta2": "furgot / furgot",
        "incorrecta3": "forgotd / forgotten"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "get",
        "respuesta": "got / got",
        "incorrecta1": "gut / gut",
        "incorrecta2": "gat / gat",
        "incorrecta3": "geit / geit"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "give",
        "respuesta": "gave / given",
        "incorrecta1": "give / give",
        "incorrecta2": "geive / geive",
        "incorrecta3": "geivd / geivd"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "go",
        "respuesta": "went / gone",
        "incorrecta1": "wen / gon",
        "incorrecta2": "gotd / gone",
        "incorrecta3": "wint / wint"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "grow",
        "respuesta": "grew / grown",
        "incorrecta1": "griw / griw",
        "incorrecta2": "growed / grown",
        "incorrecta3": "growdt / growd"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "hang",
        "respuesta": "hung / hung",
        "incorrecta1": "haung / haung",
        "incorrecta2": "hangned / hanged",
        "incorrecta3": "haned / haned"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "have",
        "respuesta": "had / had",
        "incorrecta1": "hat / hat",
        "incorrecta2": "heid /heid",
        "incorrecta3": "haved / had"
    },

{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "hear",
        "respuesta": "heard / heard",
        "incorrecta1": "heardt / heardt",
        "incorrecta2": "hiard / heard",
        "incorrecta3": "heared / heard"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "hit",
        "respuesta": "hit / hit",
        "incorrecta1": "heit / heit",
        "incorrecta2": "hate / hate",
        "incorrecta3": "heided / heided"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "hurt",
        "respuesta": "hurt / hurt",
        "incorrecta1": "hurted / hurted",
        "incorrecta2": "hurt / hurten",
        "incorrecta3": "hurteid / hurt"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "keep",
        "respuesta": "kept / kept",
        "incorrecta1": "keeped / keeped",
        "incorrecta2": "keipt / keipt",
        "incorrecta3": "kieped / kept"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "know",
        "respuesta": "knew / known",
        "incorrecta1": "knewen / knewn",
        "incorrecta2": "knowd / knowd",
        "incorrecta3": "knowded / knowed"
    },

{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "learn",
        "respuesta": "learnt / learnt",
        "incorrecta1": "learned / learned",
        "incorrecta2": "liarnd / liarned",
        "incorrecta3": "liarnt / liarnt"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "leave",
        "respuesta": "left / left",
        "incorrecta1": "left / leftd",
        "incorrecta2": "lifted / left",
        "incorrecta3": "leeft / leeft"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "lend",
        "respuesta": "lent / lent",
        "incorrecta1": "lended / lent",
        "incorrecta2": "lented / lented",
        "incorrecta3": "leint / leint"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "let",
        "respuesta": "let / let",
        "incorrecta1": "leted / leted",
        "incorrecta2": "leited / leited",
        "incorrecta3": "leded / let"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "lie",
        "respuesta": "lay / lain",
        "incorrecta1": "leiy / leid",
        "incorrecta2": "leided / leided",
        "incorrecta3": "layed / lain"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "lose",
        "respuesta": "lost / lost",
        "incorrecta1": "losted / losted",
        "incorrecta2": "losed / losed",
        "incorrecta3": "loust / loust"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "make",
        "respuesta": "made / made",
        "incorrecta1": "meik / meik",
        "incorrecta2": "maked / maked",
        "incorrecta3": "maded"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "mean",
        "respuesta": "meant / meant",
        "incorrecta1": "meaned / meant",
        "incorrecta2": "meint / meand",
        "incorrecta3": "meanted / meanted"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "meet",
        "respuesta": "met / met",
        "incorrecta1": "meeted / meeted",
        "incorrecta2": "med / med",
        "incorrecta3": "meted / meted"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "pay",
        "respuesta": "paid / paid",
        "incorrecta1": "peid / peid",
        "incorrecta2": "payed / paid",
        "incorrecta3": "peyet / peyet"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "put",
        "respuesta": "put / put",
        "incorrecta1": "puted / puted",
        "incorrecta2": "pouted / pouted",
        "incorrecta3": "putyed / putyed"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "read",
        "respuesta": "read / read",
        "incorrecta1": "riad / redded",
        "incorrecta2": "readed / readed",
        "incorrecta3": "readid / raded"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "ride",
        "respuesta": "rode / ridden",
        "incorrecta1": "roded / roded",
        "incorrecta2": "rouded / rouded",
        "incorrecta3": "roude / roude"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "ring",
        "respuesta": "rang / rung",
        "incorrecta1": "raned / raned",
        "incorrecta2": "raouned / rouned",
        "incorrecta3": "ringed / ringed"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "run",
        "respuesta": "ran / run",
        "incorrecta1": "raned / raned",
        "incorrecta2": "rouned / rouned",
        "incorrecta3": "runed / runed"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "say",
        "respuesta": "said / said",
        "incorrecta1": "sayed / said",
        "incorrecta2": "saeided / saided",
        "incorrecta3": "saitd / said"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "see",
        "respuesta": "saw / seen",
        "incorrecta1": "seid / siin",
        "incorrecta2": "seed / seed",
        "incorrecta3": "seded / sead"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "sell",
        "respuesta": "sold / sold",
        "incorrecta1": "selled / solded",
        "incorrecta2": "solded / solded",
        "incorrecta3": "sould / sould"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "send",
        "respuesta": "sent / sent",
        "incorrecta1": "sended / sended",
        "incorrecta2": "sented / sented",
        "incorrecta3": "seind / seind"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "set",
        "respuesta": "set / set",
        "incorrecta1": "seted / set",
        "incorrecta2": "seited / seitd",
        "incorrecta3": "souded / souded"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "shine",
        "respuesta": "shone / shone",
        "incorrecta1": "shined / shined",
        "incorrecta2": "shoned / shone",
        "incorrecta3": "shouned / shouned"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "shut",
        "respuesta": "shut / shuted",
        "incorrecta1": "shuted / shuted",
        "incorrecta2": "shouted / shut",
        "incorrecta3": "shout / shout"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "sing",
        "respuesta": "sang / sung",
        "incorrecta1": "sand / sung",
        "incorrecta2": "seinged / sang",
        "incorrecta3": "sangund / sangund"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "sit",
        "respuesta": "sat / sat",
        "incorrecta1": "sated / sated",
        "incorrecta2": "seat / sat",
        "incorrecta3": "sited / sat"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "sleep",
        "respuesta": "slept / slept",
        "incorrecta1": "sleeped / sleeped",
        "incorrecta2": "sleipt / sleipt",
        "incorrecta3": "sleupt / sleupt"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "smell",
        "respuesta": "smelt / smelt",
        "incorrecta1": "smelled / smelled",
        "incorrecta2": "smalled / smalled",
        "incorrecta3": "semltd / smelt"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "speak",
        "respuesta": "spoke / spoken",
        "incorrecta1": "speaked / speaked",
        "incorrecta2": "spouke / spoken",
        "incorrecta3": "speaktd / speaked"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "spend",
        "respuesta": "spent / spent",
        "incorrecta1": "spended / speint",
        "incorrecta2": "speint / spent",
        "incorrecta3": "spownt / spownt"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "stand",
        "respuesta": "stood / stood",
        "incorrecta1": "standed / standed",
        "incorrecta2": "stouded / steind",
        "incorrecta3": "steind / steind"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "steal",
        "respuesta": "stole / stolen",
        "incorrecta1": "stealed / stealed",
        "incorrecta2": "steilded / stoll",
        "incorrecta3": "stoll / stoll"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "swim",
        "respuesta": "swam / swum",
        "incorrecta1": "swmied / swimmed",
        "incorrecta2": "swimmed / swmied",
        "incorrecta3": "swamnd / swamnd"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "take",
        "respuesta": "took / taken",
        "incorrecta1": "taked / taked",
        "incorrecta2": "teiken / teiken",
        "incorrecta3": "taked / taked"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "teach",
        "respuesta": "taught / taught",
        "incorrecta1": "teached / teached",
        "incorrecta2": "teacheded / teacheded",
        "incorrecta3": "taughd / taught"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "tell",
        "respuesta": "told / told",
        "incorrecta1": "telled / tolded",
        "incorrecta2": "tolded / tolded",
        "incorrecta3": "tellen / told"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "think",
        "respuesta": "thought / thought",
        "incorrecta1": "thinked / thinkd",
        "incorrecta2": "theinded / thinked",
        "incorrecta3": "thinkd / thought"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "throw",
        "respuesta": "threw / thrown",
        "incorrecta1": "threwed / thrown",
        "incorrecta2": "throwded / threwed",
        "incorrecta3": "throwtd / thrownd"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "understand",
        "respuesta": "understood / understood",
        "incorrecta1": "understanded / understood",
        "incorrecta2": "understooded / understand",
        "incorrecta3": "understantd / understooded"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "wake",
        "respuesta": "woke / woken",
        "incorrecta1": "waked / waked",
        "incorrecta2": "wokeded / wokeded",
        "incorrecta3": "wokt / wokt"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "wear",
        "respuesta": "wore / worn",
        "incorrecta1": "wored / worn",
        "incorrecta2": "weared / wear",
        "incorrecta3": "weartd / worn"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "win",
        "respuesta": "won / won",
        "incorrecta1": "wont / wont",
        "incorrecta2": "winded / winded",
        "incorrecta3": "wonted / wined"
    },
{
        "categoria": "Irregular Verbs - P.Simple / P.Participle",
        "pregunta": "write",
        "respuesta": "wrote / written",
        "incorrecta1": "writed / writed",
        "incorrecta2": "wroted / wroted",
        "incorrecta3": "wrided / written"
    }
]
